<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nintendo-Ds on Tardigrade&#39;s dev blog</title>
    <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/tags/nintendo-ds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nintendo-Ds on Tardigrade&#39;s dev blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/tags/nintendo-ds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Nintendo DS] Negative Space</title>
      <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2008/negativespace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2008 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2008/negativespace/</guid>
      <description>Negative Space An original homebrew game for the Nintendo DS, based on the concept of negative space.
Download: NegativeSpacev2_nds.zip / NegativeSpacev2_gba.zip
Source: NegativeSpacev2_src.zip
How to play:
The whole game contains only two colors: black and white. The player controls two &amp;lsquo;blob&amp;rsquo; characters: the white blob moves in the black space, and the black blob in the white space. That&amp;rsquo;s why, empty space for one blob represents solid ground and walls for the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Nintendo DS] Everlasting Love</title>
      <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2007/everlastinglove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2007/everlastinglove/</guid>
      <description>Everlasting Love A homebrew game for the Nintendo DS.
Everlasting Love is a combination of a 2D platformer and a rhythm game, in which you have to adjust your jumps using the music. The song is Everlasting Love from the original soundtrack of We Love Katamari.
Download: Everlasting.zip / Everlasting_sc.zip / Everlasting_gba.zip
How to play :
The monkey can move right and left during jumps only. No walking. As soon as he touches a wall, he holds onto it until the next jump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Nintendo DS] Ninji &amp; Zarbi</title>
      <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/ninjizarbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/ninjizarbi/</guid>
      <description>Ninji &amp;amp; Zarbi A homebrew game for the Nintendo DS.
Download: Ninji_nds.zip / Ninji_gba.zip / Ninji_sc.zip
Source: Ninji_0.1_src.zip
At any time, the two characters Ninji (bottom screen) and Zarbi (upper screen) are located at the same place on their respective screen. You control both characters at the same time.
The aim of the game is to achieve the highest score possible, by neutralizing Bullet Bills and catching the NDSes that appear on screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Nintendo DS] Touch me</title>
      <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/touchme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/touchme/</guid>
      <description>Touch me (I&amp;rsquo;m famous) Homebrew game for the Nintendo DS.
Touch me (I&amp;rsquo;m famous) is a mix between a shooting game and a rhythm game. The song heard during the game is a sample from Sweet euphemisms by Soso.
Download: TouchMe_nds.zip / TouchMe_gba.zip
Source: TouchMe_0.1_src.zip
How to play:
Hold the DS vertically. Shoot the enemies by tapping them with the stylus, but always by the rhythm: either on the beat (indicated by the flash), or on the back beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Nintendo DS] Oil Panic DS</title>
      <link>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/oilpanicds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2006 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tardigrade-nx.github.io/2006/oilpanicds/</guid>
      <description>Oil Panic DS Homebrew game for the Nintendo DS.
Oil Panic DS is a simulator of the Game&amp;amp;Watch Oil Panic.
Download: OilPanicDS_nds.zip / OilPanicDS_gba.zip</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
